<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GoRide</string>
    <string name="AppTitle">GoRide</string>
    <string name="About">RideGo is a carpooling app for older people to help them travel through Algeria with cheap prices.</string>
    <string name="TermsConditions">By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the trade marks, copyright, database rights and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to Lamine.

        Lamine is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for its services, at any time and for any reason. We will never charge you for the app or its services without making it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.

        The GoRide app stores and processes personal data that you have provided to us, in order to provide my Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your phone and access to the app secure. We therefore recommend that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the official operating system of your device. It could make your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean that the GoRide app won’t work properly or at all.

        You should be aware that there are certain things that Lamine will not take responsibility for. Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an active internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi, or provided by your mobile network provider, but Lamine cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t have any of your data allowance left.

        If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that your terms of the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection while accessing the app, or other third party charges. In using the app, you’re accepting responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming. If you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re using the app, please be aware that we assume that you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app.

        Along the same lines, Lamine cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You need to make sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of battery and you can’t turn it on to avail the Service, Lamine cannot accept responsibility.

        With respect to Lamine’s responsibility for your use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s important to bear in mind that although we endeavour to ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we can make it available to you. Lamine accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a result of relying wholly on this functionality of the app.

        At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently available on Android – the requirements for system (and for any additional systems we decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change, and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep using the app. Lamine does not promise that it will always update the app so that it is relevant to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your device. However, you promise to always accept updates to the application when offered to you, We may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of it at any time without giving notice of termination to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.

        Changes to This Terms and Conditions

        I may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Terms and Conditions on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

        Contact Us

        If you have any questions or suggestions about my Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to contact me at ridego@lamine.me +213676515089.</string>
    <string name="PrivacyPolicy">Privacy Policy
        Lamine built the GoRide app as a Freemium app. This SERVICE is provided by Lamine at no cost and is intended for use as is.

        This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.

        If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

        The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at GoRide unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

        Information Collection and Use

        For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.

        The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

        Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app

        Google Play Services
        Firebase Analytics
        Log Data

        I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

        Cookies

        Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device\'s internal memory.

        This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.

        Service Providers

        I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

        To facilitate our Service;
        To provide the Service on our behalf;
        To perform Service-related services; or
        To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
        I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

        Security

        I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security.

        Links to Other Sites

        This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

        Children’s Privacy

        These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case I discover that a child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.

        Changes to This Privacy Policy

        I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.</string>
    <string name="smoking_allowed">Smoking Allowed</string>
    <string name="pets_allowed">Pets Allowed</string>
    <string name="instant_book">Instant Book</string>
    <string name="instant_booking">Instant Booking</string>
    <string name="request_booking">Request Booking</string>
    <string name="no_luggage">No Luggage</string>
    <string name="small_luggage">Small Luggage</string>
    <string name="medium_luggage">Medium Luggage</string>
    <string name="large_luggage">Large Luggage</string>
    <string name="booked">Booked:</string>
    <string name="driver_desc">You have no upcoming trips! added trips will be displayed here.</string>
    <string name="passenger_desc">You have no trip requests! registered trips will also be shown here.
    </string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="privacy_and_terms">Privacy and Terms</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="messages">Messages</string>
    <string name="unverified">Unverified</string>
    <string name="tomorrow">Tomorrow</string>
    <string name="more_dots">more_dots</string>
    <string name="modify">Modify</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="report">Report</string>
    <string name="your_booked">You\'re Booked!</string>
    <string name="full_trip">TRIP FULL AND READY</string>
    <string name="post_review">Post review</string>
    <string name="empty">EMPTY</string>
    <string name="review">Review</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="send_a_message">Send a message…</string>
    <string name="send_btn">send_btn</string>
    <string name="type_a_message">Type a message…</string>
    <string name="message">Message</string>
    <string name="applogo">AppLogo</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="forgot_your_pasword">Forgot your password?</string>
    <string name="dont_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="create_one">Create one</string>
    <string name="logo">logo</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="login_here">Login here.</string>
    <string name="trip_form">Trip Form</string>
    <string name="enter_your_origin_destination_and_stops_you_re_willing_to_make_to_pick_up_and_drop_off_passengers_on_the_way">
        Enter your origin, destination, and stops you\'re willing to make to pick up and drop off passengers on the way.
    </string>

    <string name="helper_icon">helper icon</string>
    <string name="ride_shcedule">Ride Shcedule</string>
    <string name="ride_schedule">Ride Schedule</string>
    <string name="enter_a_pricise_date_and_make_sure_to_post_the_correct_time_format">Enter a precise date and make sure
        to post the correct time format.
    </string>
    <string name="at">at</string>
    <string name="vehicle_details">Vehicle details</string>
    <string name="this_helps_get_more_bookings_and_gives_passengers_a_way_to_identify_your_car_during_pick_up">This
        helps get more bookings and gives passengers a way to identify your car during pick-up
    </string>
    <string name="skip_vehicle">Skip Vehicle</string>
    <string name="vehcile_image">vehcile image</string>
    <string name="vehicle_image">Vehicle Image</string>
    <string name="add_a_photo">Add a photo</string>
    <string name="model">Model</string>
    <string name="type">Type</string>
    <string name="color">Color</string>
    <string name="year">Year</string>
    <string name="license_plate">License Plate</string>
    <string name="trip_preferences">Trip preferences</string>
    <string name="this_informs_passengers_of_how_much_space_you_have_for_their_luggage_and_extras_before_they_book">This
        informs passengers of how much space you have for their luggage and extras before they book
    </string>
    <string name="luggage">Luggage</string>
    <string name="none">None</string>
    <string name="luggage_ic">luggage_ic</string>
    <string name="s">S</string>
    <string name="m">M</string>
    <string name="l">L</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="smoke_icon">smoke_icon</string>
    <string name="no_smoking">No Smoking</string>
    <string name="pet_icon">pet_icon</string>
    <string name="empty_seats">Empty Seats</string>
    <string name="we_reccomend_putting_maximum_2_people_in_the_back_to_ensure_everyone_s_comfort">We recommend putting
        maximum 2 people in the back to ensure everyone\'s comfort
    </string>
    <string name="select_a_number">Select a number</string>
    <string name="_1">1</string>
    <string name="_2">2</string>
    <string name="_3">3</string>
    <string name="_4">4</string>
    <string name="_5">5</string>
    <string name="_6">6</string>
    <string name="_7">7</string>
    <string name="price_per_seat">Price per seat</string>
    <string name="enter_a_price">Enter a price</string>
    <string name="we_suggest_prices_based_on_similar_trips_and_note_all_prices_are_in_dza">We suggest prices based on
        similar trips and note all prices are in DZA
    </string>
    <string name="origin_to_destination">Origin to Destination</string>
    <string name="consider_making_the_price_cheap">Consider making the price cheap</string>
    <string name="booking_prefrence">Booking prefrence</string>
    <string name="we_give_you_the_choice_of_either_reviewing_each_booking_or_accepting_all_bookings_instantly">We give
        you the choice of either reviewing each booking or accepting all bookings instantly
    </string>
    <string name="select_a_type">Select a type</string>
    <string name="credit_card">credit_Card</string>
    <string name="request_to_book">Request to book</string>
    <string name="you_approve_or_decline_passengers_manually">You approve or decline passengers manually</string>
    <string name="you_control_on_who_gets_in_your_car">You control on who gets in your car</string>
    <string name="passengers_are_instantly_booked">Passengers are instantly booked</string>
    <string name="sit_back_relax_and_watch_the_bookings_roll_in">Sit back, relax and watch the bookings roll in</string>
    <string name="policies">Policies</string>
    <string name="our_policies_ensure_that_both_the_drivers_and_passengers_are_happy_with_the_service">Our policies
        ensure that both the drivers and passengers are happy with the service.
    </string>
    <string name="passengers_pay_with_cash">Passengers pay with cash</string>
    <string name="all_passengers_must_pay_using_cash_to_protect_you_from_scammed">All passengers must pay using cash to
        protect you from scammed.
    </string>
    <string name="money_ic">money_ic</string>
    <string name="you_get_paid_after_the_trip">You get paid after the trip</string>
    <string name="you_ll_recieve_your_payout_after_the_trip_from_passengers_to_ensure_a_successful_trip">You\'ll receive
        your payout after the trip from passengers to ensure a successful trip.
    </string>
    <string name="flash_ic">flash_ic</string>
    <string name="ic_interested">ic_interested</string>
    <string name="you_re_committed_to_driving_when_you_post_a_trip_and_you_could_be_suspended_if_you_cancel">You\'re
        committed to driving when you post a trip and you could be suspended if you cancel.
    </string>
    <string name="trip_description">Trip Description</string>
    <string name="use_this_space_to_write_any_details_relavant_to_your_trip_for_passengers_before_they_book">Use this
        space to write any details relevant to your trip for passengers before they book
    </string>
    <string name="post_a_trip">Post a trip</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="switch_btn">switch_btn</string>
    <string name="origin">Origin</string>
    <string name="destination">Destination</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="people_driven">people_driven</string>
    <string name="star_ic">star_ic</string>
    <string name="arrow_ic">arrow_ic</string>
    <string name="car_photo">car_photo</string>
    <string name="ic_pet">ic_pet</string>
    <string name="no_smoking_inside">No Smoking Inside</string>
    <string name="type_color_year">Type, Color, Year</string>
    <string name="car_model">Car Model</string>
    <string name="_0123456789">0123456789</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="rate_the">Rate the</string>
    <string name="safety">Safety</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="timeliness">Timeliness</string>
    <string name="tell_us_more_optional">Tell us more (optional)</string>
    <string name="how_was_your_driver">How was your driver?</string>
    <string name="communications">Communications</string>
    <string name="going_somewhere">Going Somewhere?</string>
    <string name="driver_ic">driver_ic</string>
    <string name="card_arrow">Card Arrow</string>
    <string name="you_re_a_driver_with_empty_seats_that_you_re_looking_to_fill">You\'re a driver with empty seats that
        you\'re looking to fill
    </string>
    <string name="passenger_ic">passenger_ic</string>
    <string name="post_a_request">Post a request</string>
    <string name="you_re_looking_for_a_shared_ride_and_want_to_get_notified_once_it_get_posted">You\'re looking for a
        shared ride and want to get notified once it get posted.
    </string>
    <string name="plus_btn">plus_btn</string>
    <string name="car_btn">car_btn</string>
    <string name="user_img">user_img</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="female_42">Female, 42</string>
    <string name="_0_0">0.0</string>
    <string name="_0_reviews">0 reviews</string>
    <string name="_0">0</string>
    <string name="trips_traveled">trips traveled</string>
    <string name="user_rating">user_rating</string>
    <string name="dummy">dummy</string>
    <string name="joined">Joined</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone number</string>
    <string name="verified">Verified</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="reviews_0">Reviews (0)</string>
    <string name="pets">Pets</string>
    <string name="you_have_no_messages">You have no messages!</string>
    <string name="day_mon_01_at_01am">Day, Mon 01 at 01am</string>
    <string name="do_you_wanna_accept_them_into_your_trip">Do you want to accept them into your trip?</string>
    <string name="wants_to_join_your_ride">Wants to join your ride!</string>
    <string name="may_23_at_16_20">May 23 at 16:20</string>
    <string name="messages_goes_here">Messages goes here</string>
    <string name="registration_progress">Registration Progress</string>
    <string name="_0_0_0_reviews">0.0 * 0 reviews</string>
    <string name="phone_number_verfication">Phone Number Verification</string>
    <string name="please_enter_a_valid_phone_number_to_verify_your_identity">Please enter a valid phone number to verify
        your identity.
    </string>
    <string name="code_verification">Code Verification</string>
    <string name="please_enter_the_code_sent_to_you_by_an_sms_to_complete_the_registration">Please enter the code sent
        to you by an SMS to complete the registration
    </string>
    <string name="didn_t_recieve_it_in_1_minute_click_here_to_try_again">Didn\'t receive it in 1 minute?, click here to
        try again.
    </string>
    <string name="what_is_your_birthday">What is your birthday?</string>
    <string name="you_must_be_at_least_18_years_old_to_use_ridego_please_enter_your_correct_birthday_below">You must be
        at least 18 years old to use RideGo. Please enter your correct birthday below.
    </string>
    <string name="what_is_your_gender">What is your gender?</string>
    <string name="please_enter_your_gender_for_better_safety_and_specification_when_traveling">Please enter your gender
        for better safety and specification when traveling.
    </string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="are_you_a_driver">Are you a driver?</string>
    <string name="check_this_box_if_you_will_be_driving_this_will_adjust_your_prefrences">Check this box if you will be
        driving, this will adjust your prefrences.
    </string>
    <string name="write_some_interesting_things_about_you_to_help_people_understand_what_type_of_person_you_are">Write
        some interesting things about you to help people understand what type of person you are!
    </string>
    <string name="upload_a_picture_of_yourself">Upload a picture of yourself!</string>
    <string name="take_a_selfie">Take a selfie!</string>
    <string name="choose_from_photo_library">Choose from photo library</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of service</string>
    <string name="please_agree_to_our">Please agree to our</string>
    <string name="to_complete_your_registration_please_check_the_box_on_the_right">to complete your registration please
        check the box on the right.
    </string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string-array name="countries_array">
        <item>Afghanistan</item>
        <item>Albania</item>
        <item>Algeria</item>
        <item>American Samoa</item>
        <item>Andorra</item>
        <item>Angola</item>
        <item>Anguilla</item>
        <item>Antarctica</item>

    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact based on your message
        history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entries">
        <item>Entry 1</item>
        <item>Entry 2</item>
        <item>Entry 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entry_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multi_select_list_preference_default_value"/>

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="pref_header_profile">Profile settings</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="stops">Stops</string>
    <string name="app_description">GoRide is a carpooling app made for algerian older people to travel easier and
        cheaper, younger people can sign-up to drive for older people while older passengers can sign-up and search for specific trips
    </string>
    <string name="sign_up_using_email">Sign-up using email.</string>
    <string name="editpfp">editpfp</string>
    <string name="admin">admin</string>
    <string name="click_here">click here.</string>
    <string name="delete_superuser">Delete (superuser)</string>
    <string name="delete_user_as_admin">Delete user as Admin</string>
</resources>
